A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller personal papers, Ann C. Whitman - Politics, Series P FA351
Rockefeller Archive Center
- B General (Box 1, Folder 27)
  Boland, Mary K.: 1961-1962, thanks NAR for comments on her summary of book. Resignation from NAR's research staff. NAR meeting with Congressman Corbett. Borden, Frank: 1968, thanks for dinner invitation. Bosworth, Welles: 1962, NAR thanks for gift. Botelho, Viscount of: no date, sends NAR wine & photos. Bowen, Ruth: no date, thanks for NAR's gift. Bowie, W.G.: 1966, President, Albany Symphony Orchestra. Fund raising appeal. Season invitation. Bowles, Chester: 1967, Amassador to India, re: Indian development. Boyd, Betsy: 1966, NAR's thanks and gift work done. Boyden, Frank: 1960-1961, NAR thanks & congratulations on retirement. Boye, Larry: 1971, NAR autographed photo for Ball State University Choir. Boyer, Allston: 1971, invitation from Laurance Spelman Rockefeller.
- B General (Box 1, Folder 28)
  Brackett, Truman H., Jr.: 1970, Director, Dartmouth College Art Gallery. Thanks for artwork given. Braden, Thomas (Mr. & Mrs.): 1960-1970, Christmas greetings. NAR thanks for gift. Congratulations on son's birthday. Braden sale of newspaper. Bradley, Peter H.: 1959, Executive Assistant to Speaker, New York State Assembly. Bradshaw, Lester: 1966-1970, Wisconsin, Ohio politics. Primary news in Florida & Ohio. Wisconsin local election. Romney campaign in Connecticut. NAR thanks for support. Brandt, Willy: 1963-1964, Mayor of West Berlin, Germany. Berlin Cultural program, NAR declines loan of Museum of Modern Art pictures. Braune, Alexander: 1969, NAR inquiry to straw mats in hotel. Bridges, Doloris T.: 1963, New Year's greetings. Bromley, Bruce Justice: 1967, Young Republican Club activities. NAR contribution. Bronstein, Herbert: 1967, NAR introduction to Museum of Primitive Art exhibit; copy of introduction script. Brooke, Edward (Mrs.): 1971-1972, thanks NAR for contribution to Art Institute of Boston. Brooke, Edward W.: 1968, campaign. Brown, Barbara: 1961-1962, appointment with William Pfeiffer. Health Bill. Brown, H. C., Jr.: 1965, Southwestern Baptist Theological Seminary, asking for NAR to write an essay on race issues. Hugh Morrrow memo suggesting refusal. Brown, Marion Davies: no date, presidential campaign supporter. Brown, MacAlister: 1963, Director, American Studies Program, Williams College. Thanks for tour of art collection. Brownell, Herbert: 1967, congratulations on NAR inauguration. Bruce, David K. E.: 1966, Ambassador to Great Britain, re: Mrs. NAR visit to Great Britain. Bryant, Marvin: 1971, NAR thanks for gift.
- B General (Box 1, Folder 29)
  Bullis, Harry A.: 1962, thanks for NAR's comments on books. Bullock, Hugh: 1965, invitation to speak. Hinman accepts invitation for NAR. Bumpers, Dale: 1973, Governor of Arkansas, thanks for copy of report. Bundy, McGeorge: 1967, Education statement. Burbank, Kershaw: 1959, thanks for gift. Burgard, Ralph: 1970, Director, Associated Council of the Arts, Arts Project on Long Island, NY. Burns, Arthur F. (Dr.): 1967, report on fiscal issues (copy inc.). Burroughs, Robert P.: 1959, thanks for lift to Dartmouth. Trip to New Hampshire. Burton, Courtney: 1961-1967, congratulations from NAR on appointment as Chairman, Republican National Finance Committee. Republican Fund Raising Seminar. Burton, John: 1961, copy of letter from Walter Mahoney to Burton re: education financing. Butler, William: 1968, NAR letter re: planning a program. Butler, (no first name): 1967, re: "Future of Federalism." Byars, J.: 1972, thanks for trip. Byrnes, James F.: 1959, copy of Morris letter re: NAR-Byrnes "coolness," copy of Byrnes reply.
- Bader, Clay, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  NAR thanks for stay at ranch.
- Bassine, Charles, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  Re: gifts to Republican governors.
- Beaman, Orson, no date (Box 2, Folder 32)
  Head of anti-NAR group, re: Alex Zak, anti-NAR literature attached.
- Beiny, David (Mrs.), 1971 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  Her handling of London sale of items, John Davison Rockefeller, Jr.'s estate; photos of porcelain items to be sold; NAR keeping some items; pictures & Parke-Bernet appraisals; photos of items; items from Martha Baird Rockefeller's estate; NAR suggests reappraisal of some items. NAR thanks for flowers.
- Bendetsen, Karl R., 1973 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  Thanks for hospitality; NAR's acknowledge.
- Benezet, Louis T., 1973 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  President of State University of New York at Albany. Copy of letter from Lester Markel to NAR re: shortage of money for International Communications Seminars. Cancellation of seminars.
- Berezhkov, Valentin M., 1971 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  Request from International Exchange Program for Berezhkov visit to MAR, resume included.
- Berger, Andrew E., 1972 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  Secret Service agent thanks New York State Police. NAR thanks.
- Berger, Samuel D., 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  Coordinator of State Department Foreign Policy Seminar. Requests appointment for Seminar with NAR. Printed material re: Seminar course; descriptive biographies of Seminar members and leaders.
- Berlinger, George F., 1971-1973 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  Report on Welfare Rights Organization. New York State Department of Social Services. NAR thanks for letter to New York City Welfare Inspector General. Berlinger progress report. Copy to NAR of Berlinger letter to New York City Commissioner of Social Services, re: Department Management.
- Bisceglia, Philip J., 1968 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  Counsel of New York State Assembly Minority, report re: License for an insurance company.
- Bixby, Burdell, 1959-1972 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  Letter to NAR re: Commission for Youth. Republican State Committee. Thruways. Arkansas meeting. Arkansas Turnpike Authority. Dewey & Harriman autographs.
- Blinder, Albert (Mrs.), 1966-1973 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  Thanks for gifts.
- Blokhin, Academician, 1967-1972 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  President Institute of Soviet-American Relations Citizen Exchange Corps. U.S. counterpart to Institute.
- Blumenthal, Albert H., 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  Deputy Minority Leader New York State Assembly. State aid for New York City.
- Bohi, Eugene H., 1971 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  Vice President & Manager of an Albany TV station, supported NAR and Attica actions.
- Bolton, Richard H., 1971 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  Richmond County Republican Chairman, patronage.
- Boncompagne, Laetitia (Princess), 1971-1973 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  NAR thanks for hospitality. Gardening machinery sent to her.
- Borella, Victor, no date (Box 2, Folder 50)
  NAR labor advisor and Rockefeller Center Incorporated executive. Appointments. Issue propositions; union leadership, strikes.
- Boyd, Joseph H., Jr., 1973 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  Asks appointment as New York State Secretary of State.
- Boyer, Ernest L., 1961-1973 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  Higher education in New York State, Appointment of Executive Vice Chancellor.
- Boyer, Louise A., 1959-1973 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  Cornell appointments, United Nations party, contributions, gifts, budget, visit with Nixon, IBM, Mary Clark Rockefeller, Morehouse, medical schools, 1968 Republican Convention.
- Branscombe, Jean M., 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  Request for job on Laurance Spelman Rockefeller's boat.
- Braun, Ted W., 1968-1973 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  NAR California trip; Clark Clifford; Post Office; Revenue sharing; NAR thanks for gifts; State business; New York City government; Cowles communications mail fraud; Latin America Conference; advice; youth crime; insurance; drugs; Reagan; meeting with NAR; Max Kampelman; California presidential politics; Lomenzo.
- Breitel, Charles, Justice, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  Thanks for campaign support.
- Brennan, Flor, no date (Box 2, Folder 57)
  Thanks for retirement gifts and lunch.
- Brennan, Peter, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  NAR help for Labor Department job.
- Brennan, Thomas J., 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  Thanks for services.
- Bronk, Detlev W., 1969 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  President of Rockefeller University. Science advisor to NAR & New York City Mayor John Lindsay.
- Brooks, Mary (Hon.), 1971 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  Thanks for gift.
- Brydges, Earl W., 1962-1971 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  Thanks to NAR, invitation, New York State Constitutional Convention. Long Island Rail Road. NAR congratulations on Arts Council appointment, campaign contributions.
- Burden, William A. M., 1963-1973 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  President Museum of Modern Art. Thanks for gift to Museum of Modern Art. Governors Club; thanks for NAR contribution. Presidential race.
- Burger, Edward J. (Dr.), 1973 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  Resume
- Burke, Gerard P., 1971 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  White House aide, sent "Pravda" article.
- Bush, George, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  Congressman Rooney, appointments of Richard Rosenbaum & W. Steiger. NAR suggests J. Mosler for Ambassador to South Africa.
- Byrne, Christopher, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  Asks NAR ro help brother re: Medical School admission.
- C General (Box 3, Folder 68)
  Cahill, Holger (Mrs.): 1960-1973, thanks, paintings. Cake, Ralph: 1959, introductory letter for Rodman Clark Rockefeller & wife. Thank you. Calder, Elizabeth: 1967, dedication of Marymount College. Invitation to art show. Camargo, Alberto Lleras (Dr.): 1960-1968, candidate for membership in the Knickerbocker Club. Thank you. Camp, John R.: 1963-1970, available for any assistance needed. Welcome to New York. Campbell, Wallace J.: 1959, invitation to Conference & financial request. Campos, Roberto: 1963, visit to Albany. Caniff, Milton: 1967, thanks for cartoon. Cannizaro, Sal F.: 1965, tickets for Republican Club Dinner Dance. Cantril, Hadley: 1960-1969, reflections on Human venture. Served as Trustee for Institute for Social Research. Major projects of Institute. Dominican Republic Study. Notes Hungary, Czechoslovakia. International attitudes of western Europeans. Cantril, Mavis: 1963, thanks to NAR for wedding gift.
- C General (Box 3, Folder 69)
  Capehart, Homer: 1967, meeting in New York. Letter from Capehart to George Romney re: statement on Vietnam. Capps, James G.: 1961, declines the Directorship of New York State Industrial Development Commission. Card, J. V.: 1968, returns manuscript sent to Winthrop Rockefeller. Carden, Jean B.: 1963, thanks for sympathy letter. Carlebach, Julius: 1960, thanks for Christmas gift. Caron, Herbert S. (Dr.): 1963-1964, letter from F. G. Dutton to H.S. Carson re: Jewish people in Soviet Union. Request for NAR's signature on Appeal to Soviet Union. Memo from Henry Kissinger re: Appeal against anti-Semitism to Union of Soviet Socialist Republics (USSR). Carpenter, Elizabeth: 1968, thanks for meeting. Carrion, Rafael, Jr.: 1961, opening ceremonies bank in Puerto Rico. Carter, Forest S.: 1959, thanks for trip to Yellowstone. Carter, Jimmy: 1971, thanks for magazine subscription. Carter, Thelma and Elmer: 1960, thanks for Christmas gift. Carusi, Eugene: 1968, damage to tree. Casey, Dick: 1967, thanks for gift & River Club visit. Casey, William: 1972, re: Jim Mauze Caso, Ralph: 1973, sends photo. Celler, Emanuel: 1964, thanks for assisting with stay at Dorado Beach Hotel. Cermak, Ethel (Dr.): 1967, National Committee on Adoptions of American Academy of Pediatrics. Champion, George: 1967, request to be Chairman of the Taft Institute. Chapman, Bruce K.: 1960, NAR gave $500 to publish magazine, "Advance." Charlie (no last name): 1959, from Belfast, Maine, Christmas gift Choate, Arthur (Mrs.): 1962, Hyde Hall, Cooperstown, NY. Chorley, Kenneth: 1959, testimonial for Horace Albright. Clark, Russell: 1959, John M. Cabot, Ambassador to Brazil. Clark, George: 1959-1960, Christmas thank you. Photos. Clark, James: 1967, Governors Club Clark, John McLane (Mrs.): 1954, "Claremont Eagle." Clark, Jr., Percy (Mr. & Mrs.): 1960, Christmas. Clark, Percy: 1960, Christmas. Clark, William (Mr. & Mrs.): 1960, Christmas. Claude (no last name): no date, personal note (part missing). Clayton, Will L.: 1962, trade question. President's Request of Congress tariff cutting authority. Clute, Warren: 1959, thanks for ducks. Coates, Charles B.: 1959, strengthening Republican Party. Coleman, Ann: 1968, thanks for Christmas gifts. Coles, William: 1959-1962, President of Dartmouth College, correspondence with John Dickey, Dr. Cabaldon. Colt, S. Sloan: 1960, Christmas. Comay, Joan: 1965-1966, Beth Israel Hospital Dedication. National Museum Company in Israel. Christmas.
- C General (Box 3, Folder 70)
  Conklin, William (Senator): 1966, congratulations. Conley, Reg: 1963, thank you. Cooper, R. Lawlor, Esq.: 1967, thank you for invitation. Copadis, Nicholas: 1967, NAR's candidacy for President. Political career. List of NAR write-in campaign. Corbin, Sol Neil: 1962-1965, sends cufflinks, mobile. Cordier, Andrew W.: 1964, $5,000 to the Dag Hammarskjold Foundation. Cornelius, Arthur, Jr.: 1967, State Police. Corrigan, Robert: 1969, re: U.S. draft of Brazilian Boys. Coupe, Douglas C.: 1960, Christmas. Covarrubias, Rosa (Mrs.): 1959, decline to help. Cowan, Ralph W.: 1967, copy of letter to Library of Presidential Papers. Cowles, John: 1962, declines invitation. Coxe, Sally P.: 1959, appreciation. Coyne, J. Patrick: 1969, appraisal of Quality of National Intelligence Product. Craig, H.S.: 1960, re: President Lleras Camargo of Colombia. Craig, May: 1960, re: Egypt - Aswan Dam project. Craven, J. Howard: 1960, appointment with Stacy May. Creel, Dana: 1968, thank you. Crosby, Bing: 1967, photos. Creel, Dana: 1971, Joslin Diabetes Foundation, contributions by Rockefeller Brothers Fund. Cullman, Howard S.: 1963, reviews Wall Street. Curtis, Bruce: 1972, thanks during trip Grand Canyon. Curto, Ernest (Esq.): 1967, Constitutional Convention Commission.
- Calabresi, Guido (Dr.), 1973 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  Modern state in a changing world.
- Calandra, John D., 1972 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  Re: vacancies, offers names.
- Caldera, Rafael (Dr.), 1972 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  Apology for misquotes attributed to Rodman Clark Rockefeller.
- Calvert, James, Vice Admiral, 1970-1972 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  Christmas invitation to stay at NAR's house.
- Cannon, James (Mr. & Mrs.), 1973 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  Thanks. Senate Subcommittee on Intergovernmental Relations headed by Maine Senator Edmund Muskie.
- Canzeri, Joseph W., 1971-1973 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  Flowers for church. Westchester Congressional Campaign; fund raising party; harness and fixtures for stable; deer hunt.
- Carlyle, Kitty, 1966-1972 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  Thanks.
- Carter, Amon G., Jr., 1961-1973 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  Thanks for grapefruit.
- Catherwood, Martin P., 1961-1969 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  Albert-Folmer Bill. Joint New York State-New York City Committee on Manpower & Training. Labor problems.
- Catlin, George C., 1967-1973 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  Sends resume, asks to see NAR and Henry Kissinger.
- Chamberlain, Edward T., 1967-1974 (Box 3, Folder 81)
  Requests for admissions for various students to Dartmouth College.
- Chambers, Stephen, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 82)
  Requests appointment.
- Cherne, Leo, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 83)
  Requests help for appointment as President of City University of New York (CUNY).
- Childs, Marquis, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 84)
  Personal notes.
- Christison, Muriel B. (Mrs.), 1973 (Box 3, Folder 85)
  Art exhibition.
- Cole, David L., 1966 (Box 3, Folder 86)
  Medal.
- Cole, Kenneth R., 1973 (Box 3, Folder 87)
  Re: child care legislation, National Commission on Water Quality (NCWQ), Urban Development Corporation (UDC), & Division of Housing and Community Renewal (DHCR).
- Colton, George H., 1973 (Box 3, Folder 88)
  Offers views about Dartmouth.
- Colville, Lorraine, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 89)
  Thanks for hospitality.
- Conger, Clem, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 90)
  Inquiry re: tabke presented to William Henry Harrison. Asks about White House furnishings.
- Conklin, Theodore, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 91)
  Thanks for help across years.
- Connor, Robert T., 1973 (Box 3, Folder 92)
  Switching political parties, tenders resignation as Commanding Officer of New York State Militia.
- Connery, Robert, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 93)
  Asks for breakdown of NAR's year of speaking engagements.
- Cook, C. W., 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 94)
  Re: bridge across Long Island Sound from Oyster Bay to Rye, declines to serve as Director of Action for Transportation in New York State.
- Cooper, Lorraine, 1964-1968 (Box 3, Folder 95)
  Letter of recommendation, sends resume.
- Corbett, Raymond, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 96)
  Executive Council of American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO), New York State.
- Cordona, Amos, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 97)
  Trip to Rio Grande, thanks.
- Cosentino, Nick, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 98)
  Suggests appointment for Thomas Vesce to U.S. Naval Academy.
- Costikyan, Edward N., 1973 (Box 3, Folder 100)
  Charter Revision Commission.
- Cowles, Gardner (Mr. & Mrs.), 1973 (Box 3, Folder 101)
  Thanks for apples.
- Crihfield, Brevard, 1964-1973 (Box 3, Folder 102)
  Christmas greetings. Governor's Conference, trip on "Independence".
- Cullman, Edgar, 1967-1973 (Box 3, Folder 103)
  Re: New York City revenues, bootlegging cigarettes in New York State.
- Cunningham, Evelyn, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 104)
  Re: Association of Balck Assistants to Republican Governors. Women's rights. Women's Political Caucus in Albany.
- Curran, William J., 1970 (Box 3, Folder 105)
  Re: telephone bill.
- D General (Box 4, Folder 106)
  Daley, Arthur: 1968-1969, seeks appointment, asks for recommendations, sends photos, items returned. Dalrymple, Martha: 1960-1966, personal notes thanking her years of service. Correspondence regarding "Life" photos. Dalton, Ted (The Honorable): 1964, trip to Caribbean, visit to NAR's ranch in Venezuela. Daniel, Dewey: 1959, invitation declined. Danzig, Jerry A.: 1968-1973, invitation to speak, Christmas greetings, sends transcript of WNBC-TV interview. Dart, Justin: 1960, thanks for candy. Dasko, George: 1972, thanks for visit to Lake Mancos Ranch. Daughtry, Lucy: 1969, thanks for donation of $100. Davenport, Russell (Mrs.): 1972, Guarducci sculptures. David, Donald: 1959, telegram of thanks for opportunity. Davis, Joseph: 1959-1961, re: visit to Carver Federal Savings Bank, sends to reume of Joseph Davis. Davison, Marjorie: 1962, Hugh Morrow's mother-in-law, thanks for copy of the Godkin lectures. Dawson, Donald: 1967, sends photo. Deacy, William Henry: 1962, re: Dag Hammarskjold Memorial per Berent Friele. de Almeida, Francisco F.: 1968-1969, art, and visit to Lisbon. Deardourff, John: 1964-1966, political materials.
- D General (Box 4, Folder 107)
  de Barros, R. de M. (Mrs.): 1962, condolences. de Beer, Frederick (Jr.): 1964, Community Chest-Red Cross Appeal. De Bruijn: 1961, cables to De Bruijn and Governor Plattere of New Guinea re: their help at time of Michael Rockefeller's disppearance. Return of his personal effects. de Camp, Robert: 1960, re: real estate ventures. de Hoyos, Luis: 1964, appeal from the Monticello, NY mayor. de Lury, John (Mrs.): 1965, aid for sick son. de Macedo, Manuel M. (Dr. & Mrs.): 1971, re: visit to Portugal. de Michele, Peggy: 1974, letter to Senator Mike Mansfield. Dempsey, John: 1962, send Fishing and Hunting License for Connecticut. Depuy, Warner (The Honorable): 1967, recommendation for son and nephew to Dartmouth. Derby, R. Stafford: 1967, sends photos of his 50th wedding anniversary. de Roulet, Vincent: 1969, offers ideas for his replacement. Desai, Moraji: 1959, requests to see NAR, comments from Kershaw Burbank stating reasons to decline. Desir, Hermann: 1965, sends letter to Dean Rusk, NAR thanks. DeSorbo, Orlando: 1966, condolences. de Varona, Manuel (Dr.): 1963, sends report on the military power of Cuba. DeVries, Van Buren: 1966, introduction in Caracas. Dewey, Thomas E.: 1959-1967, congratulations and thanks for inclusion in 1959 Inauguration. Letter by Robert Dineen re: Insurance Department. Committee for Republican Dinner. New York State Housing Finance Agency. Gallagher's President's Report. "Rockefeller's Follies." Reform system of selecting judges. Dex, Eleanor (Mrs.): 1969, sends check for lunches of the President's Foreign Intelligence Advisory Board.
- D General (Box 4, Folder 108)
  d'Harnoncourt, Rene: 1959-1970, Christmas greetings, thanks, Museum of Modern Art (MoMA) correspondence. Dickey, Douglas: 1965, thank you for birthday card. Dickey, John: 1959-1967, correspondence regarding admissions to Dartmouth, invitations to meetings, inauguration. Dilworth, J. Richardson: 1963-1971, thanks for gift to European-American Economy Corporation. Dineen, Robert E. (The Honorable): 1966-1967, praise for designation of Charles Breitel as judge. Dirksen, Everett: 1962, Christmas greetings. Dixon, Jeane L.: 1967, requests to see NAR, declined. Dodge, Frank Schuyler (Jr.): 1967, confirming reservations at The Breakers, Palm Beach, Florida. Donnish, Julie: 1967, requests NAR meet Vice President of the Philippines in New York City. Dorman, George (Mrs.): 1967, sends check for Republicans for Progress. Dormann, Henry: 1967, sends autographed photo of NAR for Library of Presidential Papers, invitation to visit Library. Dorn, Frances E.: 1969, sends $600 to Appeal of Conscience Foundation. Douglas, Percy: 1959-1963, Christmas greetings, International Basic Economy Corporation (IBEC). Draper, Edgar: 1966, letter re: new position. Driscoll, Janet: 1966, fund raising event. Art for auction. Dryfoos, Orvil: 1961-1962, state financial assistance. Member, Board of Trustees, Darmouth College. Dudley, George: 1962, appointment with NAR, head of office for Regional Development. Dulles, Allen (The Honorable): 1959-1968, thanks for introducing Charles Lea of Syracuse to NAR, meeting, article from "Foreign Affairs." Dulles, David: 1970, re: Middle East situation. Dumas, Charles: 1968, extends courtesies from press. Dunham, Theodore (Jr.): 1968, re: establishment of an Astronomical Observatory on Mount Desert Island, Maine. Dunn, Winfield: 1973, Governor of Tennessee. Dunne, John (The Honorable): 1973, asks NAR to remain as Governor, thanks. Dunning, John R.: 1966, birthday greetings. Dyson, Charles: 1973, against Nixon.
- Davenport, John, 1966-1970 (Box 4, Folder 109)
  Information of Rhodesia, NAR helps son.
- Davenport, W. Gerald, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 110)
  Rockefeller Brothers Fund grant ot $25,000 for Opportunities Industrialization Center of America, Inc.
- Davie, Preston (Mrs.), 1959-1972 (Box 4, Folder 111)
  Chairman of Robert A. Taft Institute of Government, Political Science education, personal notes.
- Delafield, Charles B., 1972 (Box 4, Folder 112)
  Commission on the Future of Horse Racing in New York State.
- Dellenback, John, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 113)
  Cuba-U.S. Relations.
- De L'Isle (Viscount), 1973 (Box 4, Folder 114)
  Trip to England cancelled.
- Dent, Harry S., 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 115)
  Revenue sharing by State Action. Resignation as special counsel to Presdent.
- Denton, Herbert, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 116)
  Personal note to NAR.
- De Salvo, Louis, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 118)
  Re: Jack Chen's appointment as Chinese curriculum consultant for State University of New York (SUNY).
- Diamond, Henry L., 1969-1973 (Box 5, Folder 119)
  Environmental standards, environmental conservation law, Environmental Bond Issue campaign. Modern state.
- Dillon, Douglas, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 120)
  Sung Yuan porcelains.
- DiMaggio, Joseph, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 121)
  Sends autographed baseballs to NAR for sons.
- Dinerstein, Martha Lay, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 122)
  Director, State Consumer Protection Board.
- Dobrynin, Anatoly F. (His Excellency), 1970-1973 (Box 5, Folder 123)
  Ambassador of Union of Soviet Socialist States (U.S.S.R.).
- Donovan, PFC John, 1965-1967 (Box 5, Folder 124)
  Correspondence between NAR and Marine and his family.
- Donovan, Robert J., 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 125)
  Personal note, appointment.
- Doty, Robert M., 1967-1971 (Box 5, Folder 126)